There's a Princess in every girl!
Barbie: Princess Charm School is a family, animation,
fantasy film directed by Ezekiel Norton.
Blair, a waitress in the kingdom of Gardania, realises that she
strongly resembles the region's missing queen.
She then gets to go to Princess Charm School and
causes problems for the teacher.
Blair (voice), played by Diana Kaarina.
Miss Privet (voice), played by Morwenna Banks.
Dame Devin (voice), played by Nicole Oliver.
Delancy (voice), played by Brittney Wilson.
Portia / Hadley (voice), played by Ali Liebert.
Isla (voice), played by Shannon Chan-Kent.
Barbie: Princess Charm School is a 2011 animated fantasy film directed by Zeke Norton, written by Elise Allen, and
produced by Mattel Entertainment (under the name of Barbie Entertainment) with Rainmaker Entertainment.
It was released on DVD on September 13, 2011, and made its
television debut on Nickelodeon two months later.
The twentieth installment in the Barbie film series, the plot follows Blair Willows, a teenage girl living in the kingdom of Gardania,
who wins an annual lottery to attend a prestigious school where girls can train to become princesses or royal ladies.
As Blair learns the ways of being a proper princess, she uncovers the mystery
and secrets behind the kingdom's missing heiress to the throne.
The film explores themes of princess, based on toy,
school, female protagonist, 3d animation.